[Music]
Loot,
my name is Akash Kumar. I'm
from Dehradun. In
October 2021, I purchased a lemon juice plan for
₹10 and additionally, I recharged for ₹40.
I took this plan from Mr. Yogesh Kumar
Gupta, a senior sales
advisor who has been with Nibha for the past 12 years. When
Mr. Yogesh Kumar
Gupta explained the benefits of this plan,
I realized
that no other plan offers as many benefits and features.
Before this, I had a
helpline with another company, so
I later ported it to Nibha in
May 2022. My wife had a baby last month, and it was
almost nibble on top of me within half an hour.
So, I
would like to say that the service was very fast and accurate.
The way my claim was approved within half an hour,
I would like to recommend it to others.
I would also like to thank the team at Nibha.
So, I would like to thank Yogesh Kumar Gupta for helping me.
Tell me about this polythene, this village pieces,
and it proved to be exactly that and
in the future I would say to stick with this policy
and once again I
want to thank you all, I think
so much
[laughter]
[music]